# question-blanks.yml
# 4 bonus question - 8, 9, 12, 18
---
#7
- question: "nama asli dari St JPII adalah"
  answer: "Karol Josef Wojtyla"
#08
- bonus: "yes"
  question: "who is this person?"
  answer: "Mehmet Ali Agca"
#09
- bonus: "yes"
  question: "Bunda Maria menampakan diri kepada St. Catherine di sebuah kapel yang bernama ..."
  answer: "chapel of the Daugthers of Charity of SVDP"
- question: "Bunda Maria menampakan diri di Guadalupe sebanyak...."
  answer: "4 kali"
- question: "Ketika melihat Bunda Maria, Bernadette saat itu berumur.."
  answer: "14"
#12
- bonus: "yes"
  question: "What was the food of John the Baptist?"
  answer: "Locust and wild honey (mt 3:4)"
- question: "who appeared with Jesus, during transfiguration?"
  answer: "Moses and Elijah (Mt 17:3)"
- question: "Who was the highest priest at Jesus' trial?"
  answer: "Caiaphas (Mt 26:3)"
- question: "After the call of the first 4 apostles, where did Jesus the apostles go?"
  answer: "Capernaum (Mk.1:21)"
- question: "how many baskets of leftover pieces did they collect afer feeding the five thousand?"
  answer: "12 (mk 6:43)"
- question: "where did Jesus go after the feeding of the 5000?"
  answer: "bethsaida (mk 6:45)"
#18
- bonus: "yes"
  question: "to whom did Luke dedicate his gospel?"
  answer: "Theophilus (Lk 1:3)"
- question: "For how long was the heaven shut up in the time of Elijah?"
  answer: "3 years, 6 month (Lk4:25)"
- question: "In wedding of cana, how many stone water jars were there?"
  answer: "6 (Jn 2 :6)"
- question: "Where did Lazarus, brother of Mary n Martha, lives?"
  answer: "Bethany (Jn 11:1)"
